UNITE HERE Publications 6200 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE HERE Publications
2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE HERE
6200 PUBS
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Publications.
8255155
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 24, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union; UNITE HERE (Organization)
8255155
- Atlantic City Casino Strike (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Atlantic City. Casino Strike., Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: Local 54
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: Atlantic City. Casino Strike., Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Atlantic City. Casino Strike., Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: Copy 3.
- Brookfield Uniforms, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Brookfield Uniforms., Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: UNITE HERE
  - Item 2: Brookfield Uniforms., Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Conducting Your Union Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  In English, Spanish, and French
  - Item 1: Conducting Your Union Meeting., Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Author: Education and Mobilazation Department
  - Item 2: Como conducir su asamblea sindical., Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Author: Departmento de Educacion y Movilizacion
    Language: Spanish.
  - Item 3: Comment mener une asseble syndicale., Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Author: Department de l'Education
    Language: French.
- Constitution, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constitution., 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Constitution., 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Constitution., 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Constitution., 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Family and Medical Leave Act, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  In English and Spanish
  - Item 1: The Family and Medical Leave Act. La Ley de Permiso de Ausencia por Razones Mdicas y Familiares., Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Language: English;Spanish.
  - Item 2: The Family and Medical Leave Act. La Ley de Permiso de Ausencia por Razones Mdicas y Familiares., Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Family and Medical Leave Act. La Ley de Permiso de Ausencia por Razones Mdicas y Familiares., Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
- How Much Power is in a Penny?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  In English and Spanish, Local 25
  - Item 1: Local 25 Cunto Poder hay en un Cantavo?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Local 25
  - Item 2: How Much Power is in a Penny? Local 25, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Local 25 Cunto Poder hay en un Cantavo?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Local 25 Cunto Poder hay en un Cantavo?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Local 25 Cunto Poder hay en un Cantavo?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: Copy 4.
  - Item 6: How Much Power is in a Penny? Local 25, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: How Much Power is in a Penny? Local 25, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: How Much Power is in a Penny? Local 25, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Open Letter to Health Care Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Open Letter to Health Care Workers., Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Organize! Mobilize!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Organize! Mobilize! A organizarse! A movilizarse!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Organize! Mobilize! A organizarse! A movilizarse!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Stewards Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Stewards Handbook., Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Author: Education Department
  - Item 2: Manual del Delegado Sindical, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Author: Departmento de Educacion
- A Strike on May 5: Do We Have a Choice?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Strike on May 5: Do We Have a Choice?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Postcard.
  - Item 2: A Strike on May 5: Do We Have a Choice?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Postcard. Copy 2.
- The Truth About Angelika: Bad for the Community, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Truth About Angelika: Bad for the Community., Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: The Truth About Angelika: Bad for the Community., Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Unfair Labor Practice Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Blank forms
  - Item 1: Unfair Labor Pratice Report. Blank forms. Booklet., Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Unite Here!, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Volume 1: Fall 2004; in English and French; 2 copies
  - Item 1: Unite Here!, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.1 (2004:Fall)
    Language: English;French.
  - Item 2: Unite Here!, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.1 (2004:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Unite Here!, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.1 (2004:Fall). Copy 3.
- Unite Here!, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Annual Report: Fall 2005; in English and French; 2 copies
  - Item 1: Unite Here! Annual Report: Fall 2005., Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Unite Here!, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Annual Report: Fall 2006; in English and French; 2 copies
  - Item 1: Unite Here! Annual Report: Fall 2006., Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Unite Here! Annual Report: Fall 2006., Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
- A Winning Combination, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Unite Here!, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Unite Here!, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Unite Here!, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Affiliate Legal & Financial Training, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Affiliate Legal and Financial Training Seminar, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: September, 2005.
- Affiliate Legal and Financial Training, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Affiliate Legal and Financial Training Seminar, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: September 9-10, 2006.
- Affiliate Legal and Financial Training, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Affiliate Legal and Financial Training Seminar, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: September 30, 2007.
- Affiliate Legal and Financial Training, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Affiliate Legal and Financial Training Seminar, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: December 12, 2008.
- Bargaining Low Cost Health Benefits, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Bargaining Low Cost Health Benefits Workshop, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: April 17-18, 2007
- Jewish Labor Committee. Human Rights Award Dinner, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Human Rights Award Dinner, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: Jewish Labor Committee
    Notes: July 9, 2008.
- A Celebration of Women in the Labor Movement Jewish Labor Committee, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A Celebration of Women in the Labor Movement, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Language: English;Yiddish;Spanish.
- Hospitality with Dignity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Hospitality With Dignity: Ethical Workplace Standards for Hotel Housekeepers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Author: Interfaith Council on Religion, Race, Economic and Social Justice; UNITE HERE Local 19
- Fashion Center, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Fashion Center, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: The Fashion Center
    Notes: Packet of promotional information
- Conduct Unbecoming, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Conduct Unbecoming: Sweatshops and the U. S. Military Uniform Industry, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
- UNITE HERE - benefit booklets, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: UNITE HERE GHI Benefit Program Member Handbook, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Author: GHI
  - Item 2: Your UNITE HERE Health and Welfare Summary Plan Description, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Labor Council for Latin American Advancement - Gala Dinner Programs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Labor Celebration and Gala Dinner Dance, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Author: LCLAA (Labor Council for Latin American Advancement)
    Notes: January 26, 2007.
  - Item 2: Garment Industry Development Corporation 20th Anniversary Cocktail Gala, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Author: Garment Industry Development Corporation
    Notes: March 24, 2005.
  - Item 3: Labor Celebration and Gala Dinner Dance, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: January 26, 2007. Copy 2.
- UNITE HERE Constitution (draft) 2004, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: UNITE HERE Constitution, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: Draft as of June 1, 2004, 5:27 PM
- UNITE HERE - Pension Booklets, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Your Pension Benefit Summary, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Your Pension Benefit Summary, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Your Pension Benefit Summary, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: UNITE HERE Fondo de Jubilacion Nacional, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: UNITE HERE Fondo de Jubilacion Nacional, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: UNITE HERE Fondo de Jubilacion Nacional, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
- New York Metro - ARGA Joint Board News - English and Spanish, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (2005:Winter)
  - Item 2: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (2005:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (2005:Winter). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (2006:Winter)
  - Item 5: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (2006:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 6: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (2006:Winter). Copy 3.
  - Item 7: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (2007:Winter)
  - Item 8: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (2008:Fall/Winter)
  - Item 9: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (2008:Fall/Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 10: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (2008:Fall/Winter). Copy 3.
  - Item 11: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (2007:Winter). Copy 3.
  - Item 12: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (2007:Winter). Copy 2.
- NY Metro Area Joint Board News (Chinese), Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Language: Chinese.
  - Item 2: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 11: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Retiree News, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Retiree News, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Author: UNITE HERE Retirees Association
    Notes: June 2005. Spanish version dated 2004.
  - Item 2: Retiree News, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: June 2005. Spanish version dated 2004. Copy 2.
    Language: English; Spanish.
- CAFTA and Free Trade, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: CAFTA and Free Trade: What Every American Should Know, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Author: Greg Spotts
    Notes: Disinformation All Access Series
- Constitution, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Calendars, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Calendar, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Calendar, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Calendar, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Calendar, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
- The Family and Medical Leave Act, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Family and Medical Leave Act: How to Make It Work For You, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Notes: A short guide to your FMLA rights
- UNITED HERE! Annual Report, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: UNITE HERE! Annual Report 2008, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
- A Salute to Norman Hill, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: A Salute to Horman Hill, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Author: A. Philip Randolph Institute; New-York Historical Society
    Notes: November 16, 2005.
- The Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire: March 25, 1911, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Author: Serphin R. Maltese
    Notes: A Memorial Compilation and Testament to the 146 Victims, Their Families and Those Heroic Immigrants Whose Labor and Sacrifice Made America Great. March 25, 2007.
- Hotel Workers United, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Hotel Workers United, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: v.1:no.1
  - Item 2: Hotel Workers United, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: v.1:no.1. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Hotel Workers United, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: v.1:no.1. Copy 3.
- UNITE HERE Annual Report, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: UNITE HERE Annual Report 2007, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: UNITE HERE Annual Report 2007, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Your Prescription Drug Benefit Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Your Prescription Drub Benefit Handbook, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: Program II. Effective July 1, 2005.